看看这个  简直太酷了
Watch this, it's really cool.
呼叫里奥纳德·霍夫斯塔德
Call leonard hofstadter.
是否呼叫海伦·博克斯莱特纳?
Did you say "call hellen boxlightner?"
不  呼叫里奥纳德·霍夫斯塔德
No. Call leonard hofstadter.
是否呼叫坦布尔·巴德塞德?
Did you say "call temple badsaidor?"
-不是!  -让我来试试
No!  Let me try!
呼叫...
Call...
麦克夫罗诺·麦克夫鲁尼路
McFlono McFlooniloo
正在呼叫拉杰·库萨帕里
Calling "rajesh koothrappali."
真不赖啊
That's very impressive.
不过有点种族歧视
And a little racist.
如果大家玩够了"来嘲笑有缺陷的科技"
If we're all through playing "mock the flawed technology,"
是不是可以开始"光晕之夜"(游戏名)了
Can we get on with halo night?
本该8点就开始的  现在已经8:06了
We were supposed to start at 8:00. it is now 8:06.
那现在开始吧
So we'll start now.
首先我们得考虑下这已过去的六分钟要算在什么地方
First we have to decide if those lost six minutes will be coming
是游戏时间  上厕所时间还是休息吃披萨的时间
Out of game time, bathroom time or the pizza break.
就各算两分钟吧
We could split it two, two and two.
如果我们披萨吃的是沙丁鱼
If we're having anchovies on the pizza,
那从上厕所时间里拿掉两分钟恐怕不行
We can't take it out of bathroom time.
又见什么新鲜鬼了
Oh, what fresh hell is this?
-潘妮啊  进来吧  -大家好
-hey, penny. come on in. -hey, guys.
见到一分钱(潘妮的名字意为一分钱)  捡起来(暗指约会)
See a penny, pick her up,
一整天你都会交上好运
And all the day you'll have good luck.
不  你不会的
No, you won't.
我能在这里躲一会吗
Can I hide out here for a while?
当然可以  发生什么事了
Sure. what's going on?
我在内布拉斯加州时有认识个女孩  叫克里斯蒂
There's this girl I know from back in nebraska, christy.
她打电话给我  说什么"好啊  加利福尼亚怎么样啊"
She called me up, and she's like, "hey, how's california?"
我就说"棒极了"  毕竟你知道  这里不是什么内布拉斯加
And I'm like, "awesome," cause, you know, it's not nebraska.
接下去我就发现
And the next thing I know
她已经自说自话过来要跟我住一起
She's invited herself out here to stay with me.
8:08了
8:08.
反正  她今天已经到了这儿  刚才还在我房间里
Anyway, she got here today and she's just been in my apartment
说她在奥马哈上过的一个又一个的男人是怎么怎么爽法
Yakity yakking about every guy she slept with in omaha,
基本上就是奥马哈所有的男人了
Which is basically every guy in omaha,
还在那洗她的内衣裤
And washing the sluttiest
肯定是你在我浴室洗水槽里见过的最淫荡的了
Collection of underwear you have ever seen in my bathroom sink.
她是每次洗一条丁字裤还是扔一大堆进去的...
Is she doing it one thong at a time, or does she throw it all in...
...好像浓味性爱鱼羹一样?
...like some sort of erotic bouillabaisse?
-真的有必要把他的筋给搭回来  -没错
-he really needs to dial it down. -i know.
可你既然不喜欢这个叫克里斯蒂的  为什么要留她住呢?
So if you don't like this christy, why are you letting her stay?
她和我表兄订过婚
She was engaged to my cousin
在那同时又和我亲兄睡过觉  所以她算是我亲人吧
While she was sleeping with my brother, so she's kind of family.
我为我刚才的爆发道歉
I apologize for my earlier outburst.
谁还需要玩光晕呢  因为我们已经
Who needs halo, when we can be regaled
愉快并无上光荣地聆听到了奥马哈的娼妓传说
With the delightfully folksy tale of the whore of omaha?
我觉得她不会是妓女的
I don't think she's a whore.
不  没错  她绝对就是个妓女
No, yeah, she's definitely a whore.
她完全没有自己的原则
I mean, she has absolutely no standards.
某一次她在...
This one time she was at...
霍华德人呢?
Where's howard?
你好  小姐  我知道你刚来这里
Bonjour, mademoiselle. I understand you're new in town.
上帝
Oh, good grief.
难以置信克里斯蒂竟然让霍华德进了我的房间
I cannot believe christy let howard into my apartment.
难以置信人们会花钱去算命
And I cannot believe people pay for horoscopes,
不过更值得提醒的是
But on a more serious note,
现在已经8:13了  而我们还没有开始玩光晕
It's 8:13 and we're still not playing halo.
好吧  我们就玩一对一  直到他回来
Fine. we'll just play one-on-one until he gets back.
一对一?  我们从来不玩一对一  我们都是组队比赛  不玩一对一
One-on-one? we don't play one-on-one. we play teams, not one-on-one.
一对一
One-on-one.
现在我们要玩组队对抗的唯一办法是把拉杰砍成两半
The only way we can play teams at this point is if we cut raj in half.
是啊  把这外国人砍成两半
Sure, cut the foreigner in half.
他的国家还有十几亿人呢
There's a billion more where he came from.
如果你们还差一个  那我来吧
If you guys need a fourth, I'll play.
-好主意  -不
-great idea. -no.
轮子的发明是个好主意
The wheel was a great idea,
相对论是个好主意
Relativity was a great idea.
这只能算是个想法  还是很烂的一个
This is a notion, and a rather sucky one at that.
为什么
Why?
为什么?
潘妮  潘妮  潘妮
Oh, penny, penny, penny.
说吧  说吧  说吧
What, what, what?
这是个复杂的模拟对战游戏  需要琢磨很长时间
This is a complex battle simulation with a steep learning curve.
有近似无数种武器  交通工具和攻略需要掌握
There are myriad weapons, vehicles and strategies
更不用说那错综复杂的故事背景了
To master, not to mention an extremely intricate backstory.
<2-14,Penny (picking up a controller, there is the sound of an explosion from the television)>酷  看我爆了谁的头
<2-14,Penny (picking up a controller, there is the sound of an explosion from the television)>Oh cool. whose head did I just blow off?
我的
Mine.
好了  我已经明白了  各就各位吧  伙计们
Okay, I got this. lock and load, boys.
这是我们能玩组队对抗的唯一办法
It's the only way we can play teams.
是  可无论谁做她队友都会被害惨
Yes, but whoever's her partner will be hamstrung
她缺乏作战经验  更别提她...
By her lack of experience, and not to mention the fact...
你的头又爆了哈
There goes your head again.
好吧  在别人刚复活的时候就向他射击是很没体育道德的
Ok.It's not good sportsmanship to shoot somebody who's just re-spawned.
你得给他们机会来...不会吧
You need to to give them a chance to... now, come on!
拉杰  拉杰!  她把我逼到角落了  过来掩护我!
Raj, raj! she's got me cornered. cover me!
掩护你这个  无能!
Cover this, suckers!
-潘妮  你火力全开啊(直译:身上着火)  -没错  谢尔顿也是
-penny, you are on fire! -yes, and so is sheldon.
好了  就这样吧  我知道她怎样办到的  但她肯定作弊了
Okay, that's it. I don't know how, but she is cheating.
没人能长那么漂亮  游戏还玩得这么好
No one can be that attractive and this skilled at a video game.
等等  谢尔顿  回来  有件东西你忘了
Wait, sheldon, come back. you forgot something.
什么?
What?
这个等离子手榴弹
This plasma grenade.
看  你被炸得满天都是
Look, it's raining you.
你笑吧  你等着你需要技术支援的那天吧
You laugh now--you just wait until you need tech support.
天啊  他真是输不起啊  是不是?
Gosh, he's kind of a sore loser, isn't he?
老实说  他赢的时候也不怎么样
To be fair, he's also a rather unpleasant winner.
走了  玩得很愉快
Well, it's been fun.
潘妮  我们的组合很棒啊
You know Penny. We make such a good team.
或许我们什么时候可以参加一些光晕锦标赛
Maybe we could enter a couple of halo tournaments sometime.
或者我们还是过得充实点吧
Or we could just have a life.
我猜对你来说  这可以是个选择啊
I guess for you that's an option.
-晚安  里奥纳德  -晚安
-good night Leonard. -good night.
还是那句  和你聊天很愉快  拉杰
As usual, nice talking to you, raj.
你说她刚那句话是什么意思?
What do you suppose she meant by that?
她是个谜一样的人  拉杰
She's an enigma, raj.
还有一件事  潘妮  这个游戏是讲究一定规范和伦理的
And another thing--there's a certain ethic to the game, penny,
-一个良好...  -她已经走了  谢尔顿
-a well-established... -she's gone.
她可以说声再见的
She could have said good-bye.
我遇到麻烦了
Okay, I have a problem.
那叫做腕管综合症  老实说  你活该
It's called carpal tunnel syndrome, and quite frankly you deserve it.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
霍华德和克里斯蒂在...
Howard and christy are...
在我卧室里搞上了
Kind of hooking up in my bedroom.
你肯定?
Are you sure?
我是在农场里长大的
I grew up on a farm, okay?
从我听到的来看  他们要么是在做爱
From what I heard, they're either having sex
要么就是霍华德被挤奶机给夹住了
Or howard's caught in a milking machine.
如果今晚我睡在这儿你(们)介意吗?
Do you mind if I stay here tonight?
不会  你可以睡沙发  或者睡我床
No, take the couch, or my bed.
我刚买了新枕头  低致敏的
I just got new pillows. hypo-allergenic.
沙发好了
The couch is good.
稍等  里奥纳德  过来下
Hold that thought. leonard, a moment.
我猜着了  你对此有意见
Let me guess. you have a problem with this.
-从哪儿说起呢  -你说吧  你这么做简直疯了
-where do I begin? -it's up to you. crazy person's choice.
首先  我们不留人过夜的
First, we don't have houseguests.
说实话  如果我付得起房租  我会请你走的
Frankly, if I could afford the rent, I'd ask you to leave.
你的友情对我来说也很重要  还有什么要说
Your friendship means a lot to me as well. what else?
还有...
Well...
关于我们的地震补给  我们只有两人两天的装备
Our earthquake supplies. we have a two-man, two-day kit.
又怎么说
So?
因此如果发生了地震  而我们三个人被困在这儿
So if there's an earthquake and the three of us are trapped here,
到了明天下午我们就会没食物了
We could be out of food by tomorrow afternoon.
不好意思  你是在说如果我们让潘妮住这儿
I'm sorry, are you suggesting that if we let penny stay
我们可能会屈服于吃人肉?
We might succumb to cannibalism?
没人会在事情发生之前就知道它会发生
No one ever thinks it'll happen until it does.
潘妮  如果你发誓不会在我们睡着时从我们的骨头上啃肉吃
Penny, If you promise not to chew the flesh off our bones
你就可以住在这儿
While we sleep, you can stay.
-什么  -他在运用归谬反证法
-what? -he's engaging in reductio ad absurdum.
就是通过把某方的论点夸大到荒谬的地步
It's the logical fallacy of extending someone's argument
然后批判这个它的结果  这是逻辑上的谬误
To ridiculous proportions and then criticizing the result.
我不欣赏这种方法
And I do not appreciate it.
我去帮你拿毯子和枕头
I'll get you a blanket and a pillow.
好吧  既然很明显我被无视了
Okay, since I'm obviously being ignored here,
让我再说一下这里早晨的安排
Let's go over the morning schedule.
早上7:00到7:20是我用卫生间的时段
I use the bathroom from 7:00 to 7:20.
请相应地计划好你的洗漱和生理机能
Plan your ablutions and bodily functions accordingly.
请问我该如何计划好我的生理机能?
How am I supposed to plan my bodily functions?
我建议晚上11点以后不再进水
I suggest no liquids after 11:00 p.m.
-好好睡吧  -谢谢  里奥纳德
-here you go. -thanks, leonard.
错了
Wrong.
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
你的头该睡在另一边
Your head goes on the other end.
-为什么  -这是普遍的文化现象
-why? -it's culturally universal. a bed,
床  即使是临时的床
Even a temporary bed,
人们总是会把床头板放在远离门的位置
Is always oriented with the headboard away from the door.
这是古代人遵循的规则  能保护自己不受野兽袭击
It serves the ancient imperative of protecting oneself against marauders.
我愿意冒个险
I'll risk it.
还有什么需要说的吗
Anything else should I know?
是的  如果你用了我的牙刷
Yes, if you use my toothbrush,
我会从那窗户跳下去
I'll jump out that window.
请你不必参加我的葬礼  祝你晚安
Please don't come to my funeral. have a good night.
真抱歉
Sorry about that.
-没有关系  -消息提醒
-that's okay. -fyi--
他的牙刷是红色的那个  放在树脂玻璃杯里在紫外线下消毒
His toothbrush is the red one in the plexiglas case under the uv light.
知道了
Got it.
-睡得塌实  -谢谢
-sleep tight. -thanks
"睡得塌实"这个说法其实很有意思
Funny expression, "sleep tight."
这源自于床最早出现时的构造
It refers to the early construction of beds
就是把绳子互相系紧了悬挂起来  在上面放个床垫
Which featured a mattress suspended on interlocking ropes,
所以偶尔...
Which would occasionally...
睡得塌实
Sleep tight.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
自从我们住进这里  每个星期六
Every saturday since we've lived in this apartment
我都是6:15醒来  为自己倒一碗麦片
I have awakened at 6:15, poured myself a bowl of cereal,
在里面加四分之一杯2%脂的牛奶
Added a quarter cup of two percent milk,
坐在这张沙发的这一头  调到BBC美国频道
Sat on this end of this couch, turned on bbc america,
收看"神秘博士"(英国著名科幻剧)
And watched doctor who.
潘妮还在睡呢
Penny's still sleeping.
自从我们住进这里  每个星期六
Every saturday since we've lived in this apartment
我都是6:15醒来  为自己倒一碗麦片
I have awakened at 6:15, poured myself a bowl
我知道了  你自己房间里有电视啊
I know. you have a tv in your room.
你为什么就不能在床上吃早餐呢
Why don't you just have breakfast in bed?
因为我既没有生病伤残  也不是一个庆祝母亲节的女人
Because I am neither an invalid, nor a woman celebrating mother's day.
几点了?
What time is it?
6:30左右
Almost 6:30.
我睡了整整一天?
I slept all day?
不  是早晨6:30
No, it's 6:30 in the morning.
你们到底有什么毛病?
What the hell is your problem?
好了  这碗麦片已经丧失其所有分子完整性
Okay, this cereal has lost all its molecular integrity.
现在我碗里的是一团团麦片糨糊
I now have a bowl of shredded wheat paste.
好  小怪物们
Hola, nerd-migos.
你们这群人为什么会讨厌睡觉呢
Why do you people hate sleep?
你穿的是我的浴袍吗
Are you wearing my robe?
是的  抱歉  我会洗干净的
Yeah. sorry, I'll have it cleaned.
没关系  你留着吧
That's okay, keep it.
-克里斯蒂呢?  -在洗澡
-where's christy? -in the shower.
对了  你哪儿买的丝瓜络手套
By the way, where did you get that loofah mitt?
你的能够到一些我的碰不到的地方
Yours reaches places that mine just won't.
你用了我的丝瓜络?
You used my loofah?
更准确地说  是我们用了你的丝瓜络
More precisely, we used your loofah.
我把她头上死皮都去干净了
I exfoliated her brains out.
那个你也留着吧
You can keep that, too.
那看来我们得谈谈你的那些绒毛熊
Then we'll probably need to talk about your stuffed bear collection.
霍华德
Howard!
在这儿  夫人
In here, milady!
我的小引擎在这儿啊
Here's my little engine that could.
我有本心爱的小人书我再也不会看了
There's one beloved children's book I'll never read again.
你好  我是克里斯蒂
Hi. christy.
我是里奥纳德
Leonard.
-我是谢尔顿  -对啊
-i'm sheldon. -right.
你就是霍华德的随从
You're howard's entourage.
对了  克里斯蒂  你们接下去准备如何
So, christy, what are your plans?
霍华德说他要带我去比佛利山庄购物
Howard said he'd take me shopping in beverly hills.
好啊  不  我意思是说准备去哪里住
Yeah, no, I meant plans to find someplace to live.
而不是跟我一起  不是说我不乐意和你们一起
Other than with me. not that I don't love having you,
只是...地方有点挤
But it's... it's a little crowded.
潘妮  我们永远欢迎你和我们一起住
Penny, you're always welcome to stay with us.
真棒啊  我们这现在经营起小旅馆来了(两个B代表床和早餐)
Oh, terrific. now we're running a cute little b & b.
让我来跳出框框  想些别的办法
Let me offer a little outside-the-box thinking here.
为什么克里斯蒂不和我住一起呢
Why doesn't christy stay with me?
-因为你和你妈住一起  -才不是呢
-you live with your mother. -i do not.
我妈和我住一起
My mother lives with me.
好  都解决了  克里斯蒂和霍华德一起住
Then it's all settled. christy will stay with howard,
潘妮可以回她房间了
Penny can go back to her apartment,
而我可以观看后24分钟的"神秘博士"了
And I'll watch the last 24 minutes of doctor who.
即使就现在而言  更像是"何必呢博士"
Although at this point, it's more like doctor why bother?
-谢尔顿  你不能就这么发号施令...  -不许再说了!  都给我走!
-sheldon, you just can't dictate... -no more talking! everybody go!
你觉得怎么样?  想不想我重新修缮下沃尔维茨之家?
So what do you say? want to repair to casa wolowitz?
那是什么  一家墨西哥熟食店?
What is that, like a mexican deli?
不好意思  我应该早点说的
I'm sorry, I should have mentioned this earlier.
我姓沃尔维茨
My last name is wolowitz.
真是太妙了
That's so cool.
我上的第一个犹太人
My first jew.
我看是因为那里没有很多符合犹太人口味的内布拉斯加人
I imagine there aren't very many kosher cornhuskers.
你还是会带我去购物吧
But you're still taking me shopping?
你想做什么都可以
Anything you want.
好  我去收拾东西
Okay, I'll go pack my stuff.
等人类克隆技术完善了  我要去订一打这样的
When they perfect human cloning, I'm going to order 12 of those.
霍华德  你看不出她在利用你吗?
Howard. Can't you see she's using you?
管它呢?  昨晚她把上衣脱掉我都哭了
Who cares? last night, she pulled off her blouse and I wept.
听着  霍华德  我了解她  她可以和任何人上床
Look, Howard. I know her. okay? she'll have sex with anyone,
只要那些人一直给她买东西
As long as they keep buying her things.
-真的?  -是啊
-really? -yeah.
好啊!
Yea!
如果你不介意的话  我现在有些犹太教的成年礼要去兑现
If you'll excuse me, I have some bar mitzvah bonds to cash.
抱歉  没有沃尔维茨我们办不成
I'm sorry, we cannot do this without wolowitz.
没有沃尔维茨我们就没法点中国菜?
We can't order chinese food without wolowitz?
我来说给你听听
Let me walk you through it.
我们平时一直这么点的
Our standard order is,
开胃菜是蒸饺  然后点左宗棠鸡
The steamed dumpling appetizer, general tso's chicken,
芥兰牛肉  龙汁虾仁
Beef with broccoli, shrimp with lobster sauce
还有杂菜捞面
And vegetable lo mein.
你发现问题了吗
Do you see the problem?
我看见了一位问题
I see a problem.
我们整个点菜是以四个蒸饺  四个主菜
Our entire order is predicated on four dumplings and four entrees
四个人吃为基础的
Divided amongst four people.
-那我们就点三个主菜咯  -可以
-so, we'll just order three entrees. -fine.
你想去掉哪个菜  那个多出来的蒸饺又归谁呢
What do you want to eliminate? and who gets the extra dumpling?
我们可以把它一切三啊
We could cut it into thirds.
那它就不再是蒸饺了  一旦你切开
Then it's no longer a dumpling. once you cut it open it is,
它最多就是一个无上皮的小三明治
At best, a very small open-faced sandwich.
好啊  伙计们
Hi, fellas.
你们那位自以为会说中文的讨厌鬼哪去了
Where's your annoying little friend who thinks he speaks mandarin?
他把个人需要置于集体利益之上了
He's putting his needs ahead of the collective good.
在他的老家  这该当死罪
Where he comes from, that's punishable by death.
我老家是萨克拉门托
I come from sacramento.
我们能不能点一份蒸饺  但只要三个不用四个
Can we get an order of dumplings but with three instead of four?
不能换
No substitutions.
这不是换  这是减量
This isn't a substitution. it's a reduction.
好吧  不能减量
Okay. no reductions.
好吧  帮我们点三份蒸饺
Fine. bring us three orders of dumplings.
-一共12个  我们每人四个  -那行啊
-that's 12. we'll each have four. -that works.
如果我们吃蒸饺吃饱了  我们就得再去掉一道主菜
If we fill up on dumplings, we need to eliminate another entree.
不能去掉
No eliminations.
如果有吃下来多余的  我们就打包带回家好了
If we have extra, we'll just take the leftovers home.
那怎么分呢?  我已经说了  没有沃尔维茨我们办不到
And divide it how? I'm telling you, we cannot do this without wolowitz.
沃尔维茨和他新女友在一起
Wolowitz is with his new girlfriend.
如果你同意我请潘妮来的话  那就有你所要的第四个人了
If you had let me invite penny, then you would have had your fourth.
你有见过潘妮吃中国菜吗
Have you seen penny eat chinese food?
她是用叉子的  她吃蛋皮春卷还要蘸两次酱
She uses a fork and she double-dips her egg rolls.
-我们不点蛋皮春卷  -没错
-we don't order egg rolls. -exactly,
但如果她在这儿我们就得点了
But we'd have to if she was here!
我们能不能快点决定
Can we please make a decision?
不光印度那儿有孩子在挨饿
Not only are there children starving in india,
这儿还正有一个印度人在挨饿
There's an indian starving right here.
这样吧  索性我们去吃印度菜
There's an idea. why don't we just go out for indian food?
你们真是有意思
You're nice boys.
我看这么着吧
Tell you what I'm going to do.
我给你们上四个蒸饺
I'm going to bring you the four dumplings.
等我待会儿走过来时  或许我被绊一跤
When I'm walking over to the table, maybe I get bumped,
里面一只蒸饺掉到地上  没人知道嘛
One of the dumplings fall to the floor. no one has to know.
我会知道的
I'll know.
-点汤怎么样  -对  汤我们总是能分的
-how about soup? -yeah, we can always divide soup.
馄饨怎么办
What about the wontons?
是你们啊  什么事
Hey, guys, what's up?
今晚是光晕之夜
It's halo night.
是吧  不错啊
Yeah. OK.
怎么?
So?
因为沃尔维茨整天都陪着你那朋友克里斯蒂...
With wolowitz spending all of his time with your friend christy...
她不是我朋友
She's not my friend.
朋友是不会把朋友的可爱小熊弄得都浑身湿答答的
Friends do not get their friends' care bears all sweaty.
没错  总之  因为沃尔维茨忙着干别的
Right. anyway, uh, with wolowitz occupied elsewhere,
我们有件事想请求你
We had something we wanted to ask you.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
在
Yes.
潘妮
Penny.
如果你愿意成为我们光晕团队的
We would very much appreciate it
第四位队员  我们会非常高兴
If you would be the fourth member of our halo team.
我想我不用提这是一种何等的荣幸了
I don't think I need to tell you what an honor this is.
真是太好了  但我要出去和一个女伴跳舞了
That's so sweet, but I'm going out dancing with a girlfriend.
你不能出去  这是光晕之夜啊
You can't go out; it's halo night.
-对潘妮来说  这是跳舞之夜  -你每周三都去跳舞?
-well, for penny, it's dancing night. -you go dancing every wednesday?
-不是  -那这就不能叫"跳舞之夜"
-no. -then that's not "dancing night."
这样  我明天和你们玩怎么样
Look, Why don't I play with you guys tomorrow?
今晚才是光晕之夜  怎么像对牛弹琴
Tonight is halo night. it's like talking to a wall.
够了  谢尔顿  看来你和我又要对着干了
All right, now, sheldon, you and I are about to have a problem.
谢尔顿  你忘了我们排练过的
Sheldon, remember, we role-played this.
是  可你没像她这么完全不讲理啊
Yes, but you didn't portray her as completely irrational.
好了  伙计们  我要走了
All right, fellas, I gotta go.
你们好好玩
But good luck.
或许我们该问问
Maybe we should've asked her
是否可以跟她和她的女伴一起去跳舞
if we could go dancing with her and  girlfriend.
好吧  先假设我们会跳舞  实际上我们还不会
OK. Assuming we could dance-- which we can't--
我们有三个人  而她们只有两个
There are three of us and two of them.
又如何
So?
意味着又要上演一遍中国餐馆事件
It's the chinese restaurant all over again.
我保证把一个蒸饺切成三份
I assure you that cutting a dumpling in thirds
比起一个男人要和0.67个女人跳舞来说
Is child's play compared with three men
那还算是小孩子把戏
Each attempting to dance with 67% of a woman.
上帝保佑  谢尔顿  你要把我逼疯了
For god's sakes, sheldon, you're driving me crazy!
你这不是在生我的气  先生  你这是在生数学的气
Your anger is not with me, sir, but with basic mathematics.
我蛮肯定我这是在生你的气
I'm pretty sure my anger is with you.
我们到底怎么了  我们正在分崩离析
What's happening to us? we're falling apart.
-你准备打给谁  -唯一一个能
-who are you calling? -the only man who can restore
让我们这里稍显一点平衡的人
Any semblance of balance to our universe.
你好  我是霍华德·沃尔维茨
Hi, this is howard wolowitz.
我是克里斯蒂·范德贝尔特
And this is christy vanderbelt.
我们现在不能接电话  因为我们正在做爱!
We can't get to the phone right now because we're having sex!
你不会就拿这个做留言吧
You're not going to put that on your message, are you?
当然不会  只是开个玩笑  我会重新录
Nah, I'm just kidding. I'll re-record it.
谢尔顿  你得三思  你这是让霍华德在性爱与光晕之间
Sheldon, think this through. you're going to ask howard to choose
做出抉择
Between sex and halo.
不  我是让他在性爱与光晕Ⅲ之间做出抉择
No, I'm going to ask him to choose between sex and halo three.
就我所知  性爱还没有被升级到
As far as I know, sex has not been upgraded
拥有高清图像以及加强版武器装备
To include hi-def graphics and enhanced weapon systems.
你说的对  性爱只是裸体  高潮  还有人与人自然的交流
You're right, all sex has is nudity, orgasms and human contact.
说的正是
My point.
你就不能偶尔把该死的塑料纸撕下来吗!
You can take the damn plastic off the couch once in a while!
干吗  这样你和霍华德就可以在上面搞了?!
Why, so you and howard can hump on it?!
女士们  女士们  我想肯定还是有折中的办法
Ladies, ladies, I'm sure there's a middle ground.
住嘴  霍华德
Shut up, howard!
你们慢慢说  我出去骑小摩托转一圈
You guys talk. I'm gonna take my scooter out for a little spin.
你开心了?  你把你自己儿子赶出家门了
You happy? you drove your own son out of the house.
你为什么不...
Why don't you stop...
你们在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
今晚是光晕之夜啊
It's halo night.
他不是个男人  他只是个白痴
He's not a man, he's a putz!
你别用那口气跟我说话  你个骗财女!
And don't you take that tone with me, you gold digger!
-你说我什么?  -你听到了
-what'd you call me? -you heard me!
我还要告诉你  你找错对象了
And I'll tell you something else, you're barking up the wrong tree.
因为只要让我再见到你  我遗嘱里就没有霍华德这个名字
Cause as long as you're around, howard is out of the will!
我告诉你  我有更好的人选  我走了
You know what? I got better offers. I'm outta here.
这就对了  回巴比伦(那里盛产妓女)去吧  你个妓女
That's right. go back to babylon, you whore!
光晕之夜  是吧
So, halo night, huh?
我还以为她是奥马哈来的妓女
I thought she was the whore of omaha.
谢尔顿  他就在你射程之内  射击!  他正在给等离子来福枪充电
Sheldon, you got him in your sights! fire! he's charging his plasma rifle!
我现在不能射击  我正隐身着!
I can't shoot now. I'm cloaking!
-拉杰  快干了谢尔顿  -我看不见他!
-raj! kill sheldon! -i can't see him!
所以这才叫做隐身  呆子
That's why they call it cloaking, dead man!
-那扔手榴弹啊!  -我用完了!
-start throwing grenades! -i'm all out!
伙计们  我和我朋友们跳舞跳累了
Hey, guys. my friends and I got tired of dancing,
所以我们过来想和你们做爱
So we came over to have sex with you.
拉杰  跳到坦克里来!
Raj, hop in the tank!
-我们说好不准用坦克的!  -都死了还讲什么规则!
-we said no tanks! -there are no rules in hell!
该死的  医疗装备!  我需要医疗装备!
Son of a bitch. med pack! I need a med pack!
我说的吧
Told ya.
那里有个狙击兵  快用你那火箭筒!
There's a sniper. use your rocket launcher!
只有你在对我嚷嚷  我已经没子弹啦!
All I've got is a needler and I'm all out of ammo!
现在你去死吧
And now you're out of life.
你干吗按暂停?
Why'd you hit pause?
我好像听到...什么声音
I thought I heard... something.
什么?
What?
没什么  算了  继续吧
No, never mind. It's all right. Go.